

Seeking roles in Full Stack Development, Web Development, Bug fixing, Troubleshooting, Requirements Gathering, Coding, Unit Testing, Production Support, Core Java, Spring, Angular, NoSql, HTML, CSS, Jquery, Type Script, Java Script, MVC.



Current Location: Pune Total Experience: 0 Year(s) 9 Month(s)

Pref. Location: Nagpur,Pune Highest Degree: PG Diploma [Advance Computing]

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Full Stack Developer, Software Developer, Full Stack Development, Web Development, Bug

fixing, Troubleshooting, Requirements Gathering, Coding, Unit Testing, Production

Support, Core Java, Spring, Angular, NoSql, HTML, CSS, Jquery, TypeScript, JavaScript, MVC

Verified : Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 21-Jan-21

Summary

Innovative Web Developer with 8 months of experience in website design for an international Project . Demonstrated talent for front and back-end web development to optimize online presence. Seasoned expert in languages such as HTML, CSS , Jquery and JAVA as well as scripting languages TypeScript and JavaScript. Also familiar with latest frameworks such as SPRINGBOOT(Micro-sevices) , Angular 8(front-end) and MVC , their lifecycle and Architecture. Properly qualified and certified Form C-DAC(E-city) with PG-diploma in advance computing.

Work Experience

Reward360 as Jr full stack developer Sep 2019 to May 2020

jr.full stack java developer

Reward360 as Junior Java Developer Sep 2019 to May 2020

jr java full stack developer

Reward360 global Private Ltd. as Full Stack Developer

Sep 2019 to May 2020

Worked in a small team which Developed an e-commerce(Redemption Platform) website for Standard Chartered Bank which will be used across five countries.

Updated Admin Portal and Customer Portal sites for Standard Charted Banks Redemption platform which had multiple vendors as well as airline partners Internationally.

Majorly worked on Bug fixes and Troubleshooting Critical and High Priority Issues for user-oriented visuals and features using front-end languages, including HTML, CSS and JAVASCRIPT, in Admin Portal and Angular 8 framework for Customer Portal.

Used various technologies, including Angular and MVC Framework (front-end), Spring-Boot Framework(Back-end), ORACLE and MONGODB(data-base) to make code repairs for corporate website.

Pitched in to assist senior developers to meet pressing deadlines during under-staffed periods.

Conducted testing after bug fixes to deliver proper browser functionality.

Collaborated with in-house web designers to innovative, align UI design and worked under the guidence of senior developers to implement and change validations where ever required.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from kalinga deemed University Raipur in 2018

PG: PG Diploma (Advance Computing) from Center For Development Of Advance Computing in 2019

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Seed certified technology specialist-java

IT Skills

Skill Name	Version L	ast Used	Experience
C , C++ , CoreJava, Advance-Java			
Spring FrameWork, Angular 7,Sql , NoSql			
Html, CSS and javascript			
Oracle and MongoDB			
spring-boot framework			
Angular and MVC Framework			

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Marathi				

Projects

Project Title: Credit Card Fraud Detection

Client: cdac

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: Jun 2019 - Aug 2019

Onsite / Offsite: Onsite

Project Details: Farud detection in credit and debit card project using risk engine

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Physically Challenged: No

. . _ _

Countries: India

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time